I used to shut my door
While my mother screamed in the kitchen
I'd turn the music up
Get high and try not to listen
To every little fight
'Cause neither one was right
I swore I'd never be like them
But I was just a kid back then
The older I get, the more that I see
My parents aren't heroes, they're just like me
And loving is hard, it don't always work
You just try your best not to get hurt
I used to be mad, but now I know
Sometimes it's better to let someone go
It just hadn't hit me yet
The older I get
I used to wonder why
Why they could never be happy
I used to close my eyes
And pray for a whole 'nother family
Where everything was fine
One that felt like mine
I swore I'd never be like them
But I was just a kid back then
The older I get, the more that I see
My parents aren't heroes, they're just like me
And loving is hard, it don't always work
You just try your best not to get hurt
I used to be mad, but now I know
Sometimes it's better to let someone go
It just hadn't hit me yet
The older I get
The older I get, the more that I see
My parents aren't heroes, they're just like me
And loving is hard, it don't always work
You just try your best not to get hurt
I used to be mad, but now I know
Sometimes it's better to let someone go
It just hadn't hit me yet
The older I get